https://www.dlhonline.co.uk/privacy-policy

Menu
Close
0View Cart (0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
View Quote Request (0)
You have no items in your quote.
Search:
links
Login/Register
My Saved Items (0)
Product Compare (0)
You have no items to compare.
0View Cart (0)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
View Quote Request (0)
You have no items in your quote.
Dale Lifting Online
Dale Lifting Online
Search:
Handrail Tubes & Clamps Accessories
Ready-made handrails for mezzanine and platforms to BS EN ISO 14122-3:2016
View All Vacuum Lifting
My Saved Items (0)
Compare (0)
My Account
Blog
By Brand
Bushey Hall WinchmasterCamlok Lifting ClampsCodiproColumbus MckinnonCrosbyDale LiftingEclipse MagneticsEepos CranesErikkilaGIS Globestock Safety EquipmentHaaconWilliam HackettInvicta Fork Lift AttachmentsKuplexLHS - BUX MagnetsLifts AllAutomotive Industry Metal IndustryBeverage IndustryFood and Pharmaceutical industriesMezzbarriersNikoPewagPfaff SilberblauPfaff Silberblau Lifting WinchesPfaff Silberblau Trucks & Lift TablesPfaff Silberblau Jacking EquipmentRaptorRaptor Drum Handling EquipmentRaptor Fork Lift AttachmentsRaptor Hydraulic and Mechanical Jacking EquipmentRaptor Lifting EquipmentRaptor Material Handling EquipmentRidgegearRidgegear AccessoriesRidgegear Complete Height Safety KitsRidgegear Safety HarnessesRidgegear Safety LanyardsRUD ChainsRUD Lifting Points BoltedRUD Lifting Points WeldedSchillingSteermanStraightpointSumnerTawi Lifting TechnologyTawi Overhead Crane SystemsTAWI Electric Hoists with GrippersTAWI Vacuum LiftersTawi Mobile Lifting TrolleysTiger LiftingTractelTirfor Lifting and Pulling EquipmentTopal Lifting Clamps, Magnets and BeamsTractel Load Indicators and Load LimitersWarriorVaculexVaculex Vacuum Lifter RangeVaculex - For Your IndustryVaculex Cranes & Overhead SystemsYoke
Lifting, Hoisting and Winching
HoistsElectric HoistsManual Chain HoistsPneumatic HoistsAll Hoist AccessoriesWinchesElectric WinchesManual Drum WinchesPneumatic WinchesSpecial Purpose WinchesChandelier / Lighting WinchesCable PullersWire Rope Pulleys, Divertor & Snatch BlocksWire Rope & AccessoriesBeam Trolleys & ClampsClamps, Grabs & MagnetsChain, Synthetic & Wire Rope Lifting SlingsChains SlingsSynthetic ( Web & Round )
Slings Wire Rope SlingsLifting Beams & Spreader BeamsLifting ShacklesCrane Forks and SkipsEyebolts, Eyenuts and Bolted Load RingsLifting Eyes and LugsLifting HooksTool Spring BalancersLoad Arresters
Material Handling
Jacking EquipmentHydraulic Systems & ToolsDrum & Cylinder HandlingCylinder HandlingDrum Handling Trucks, Trolleys and CradlesDrum Lifting AttachmentsFork Lift Truck Drum AttachmentsReel and Roll HandlingSack and Bag HandlingScales & Load Cells / IndicatorsVacuum HandlingWaste & Materials Handling and Recycling Skips and BinsBox and Carton HandlingFurniture Movers & Crate MoversForklift Jibs, Lifting Beams and AttachmentsMaterial Lifters and Lift TablesCargo HandlingChain Binder SystemsRatchet StrapsPlatform Trucks and TrolleysPallet HandlingStandard Hand Pallet TrucksHand StackersPallet Safety GatesStatic Pallet Lift TablesSpecial Application Pallet TrucksMachinery Skates & Skids
Handrail Systems
Handrail tubes and tube clampsReady made posts and handrail kits for level surfacesAssist Handrail Tubes & Clamps Accessories Ready-made handrails for mezzanine and platforms to BS EN ISO 14122-3:2016Safety Pallet Gate Systems in conformance with ISO 14122-3:2016Warehouse barriers and upright guards
Height Safety Equipment
Fall Arrest BlocksHeight Safety KitsHeight Safety AccessoriesRescue EquipmentSafety HarnessesSafety LanyardsWork Positioning
Cranes
Jib CranesOverhead Crane SystemsMobile & Portable GantriesLifting DavitsThern Lifting DavitsThern First Mate Series 5PF5 (Up to 385 kg capacity) Lifting Davit with Manual or Electric WinchDavit FinishBase Options Pedestal BaseBase Flush MountedBase Wall mountBase Fixing Anchor KitsWheeled base with pedestal mountWinch modelUpper Limit SwitchWire ropeSwivel lockDrill Driver Kit for M2 - 4WM2-K winchHeadache ballCable spoolRope keeperCertificationThern Commander Series 5PT5 (Up to 295 kg kg capacity) Lifting Davit with Manual or Electric WinchDavit FinishBase Options PedestalBase Flush MountedBase Wall MountBase FixingsWheeled Base Pedestal MountWinch ModelUpper Limit SwitchWire RopeSwivel LockDrill Driver Kit for M2 - 4WM2-K winchHeadache BallCable spoolRope KeeperCertificationThern Commander Series 5PT10 (Up to 544 kg capacity) Lifting Davit with Manual or Electric WinchDavit FinishBase Options Pedestal BaseFlush BaseWall mountBase extensionWheeled base with pedestal mountWinch modelWire ropeOptions - Roller bearingHeadache ball (Keeps wire taut with no load)Drill DriveWire Rope SpoolerWire Rope Keeper PlateCertificationThern Commander Series Model 5PT20 (Up to 907 kg capacity) Lifting Davit with Manual or Electric WinchDavit FinishBase Options Pedestal BaseFlush BaseWall mountBase extension Wheeled base with pedestal mountWinch modelWire ropeOptions - Roller bearingHeadache ball (Keeps wire taut with no load)Drill DriveCable spoolWire Rope Keeper PlateCertificationThern Admiral Series 5PT30 (Up to 1361 kg capacity) Lifting Davit with Manual or Electric WinchCrane FinishBase Options - PedestalBase Flush MountedBase - Wall MountedWinch Type / FinishUpper Limit SwitchWire Rope Headache BallCertificationThern Captain Series 5FT20 (Up to 907 kg) Stationary Lifting Davit Cranes with Manual or Electric WinchCrane FinishWinch ModelDrill DriveUpper Limit SwitchWire Rope Headache BallCertificationThern Captain Series 5FT25 (Up to 1270 kg) Stationary Lifting Davit Cranes with Manual or Electric WinchCrane FinishWinch ModelDrill DriveUpper Limit SwitchWire Rope Headache BallCertificationCMU Lifting DavitsUK Lifting DavitsLifting Shearlegs and Confined Space Recovery TripodsHydraulic Workshop Cranes & Engine Hoists
Vacuum Lifting
By IndustryAutomotive ComponentsBeer and BeveragesClean rooms - Food / Pharmaceutical Concrete, Glass & Building ProductsDoors and WindowsLogistics and TransportationManufacturingMetal and EngineeringPaper and WoodWarehouse and StorageBy ApplicationBarrels and KegsBoards and Sheet MaterialsBottles and Liquid ContainersBox and Carton LiftingDrum and Tub LiftingGlass LiftingMetal ComponentsPaper Reels and RollsRotating and PouringSack and Bag Lifting
UK Lifting Davits
Our services
Training courses
Design, manufacture and installation
Lifting equipment repairs
LOLER and In-use inspection services
Onsite servicing, repairs and breakdown
On-site testing
Privacy Policy
Product was successfully added to your shopping cart.
Go to cart page
Continue
This privacy policy sets out how DLHonline uses and protects any information that you give DLHonline when you use this website.
DLHonline is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
DLHonline may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name and payment details
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
To process your order and obtain payment
Internal record keeping
We may use the information to improve our products and services
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Here at DLHonline we are committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of all our customers (and visitors). The information we collect from customers when making a purchase from our store is used for billing and administration purposes only and will be kept entirely confidential. Any contact information collected will expressly be contact details and payment information (such as credit or debit card). We guarantee that none of this information will be passed onto third parties. For the purposes of analysing web traffic and to improve the site in general we may store information regarding visitor’s ISP domain, the time accessed and the pages visited. Should you have any queries relating to our Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@dale-lifting.co.uk
Cookies set by DLHonline
Cookies are small files placed on your web-enabled device while browsing the internet which aim to improve your browsing experience. For example:
Information you’ve already entered can be remembered so you don’t have to enter it again the next time you visit.
Similarly, your login details such as username and password can be temporarily saved so you don’t have to enter them each time you visit.
They can also measure site traffic to help us make the service we provide even better.
For more information on these small files, you can read more on the Direct Gov website by following this link: Internet browser cookies -what they are and how to manage them.   Below we have listed the cookies used on this website as well as their use and how long they will last.
Cookies Collected By DLHonline
NamePurposeContentExpires
ekm_dalelifting
Temporary cookie generated to test if cookies are enabled on the visitors browser.
TestCookies=ACTIVE&RS=FALSE& logged_in=dalelifting&ServerID=***
72 hrs (3 days)
ekm_pp_dalelifting
Stores a unique reference to visitors cart contents. Stores authentication details for customer logged in section.
Unique ID
On Exit
ekm_tmp_ORDERNUMBER
Stores a reference to the visitors order number after an order has been generated.
Unique ID
On Exit
Cookies Collected By Third Parties
Third PartyNamePurposeInfo
Google
_utma _utmb _utmc _utmz PREF NID
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to create reports and to help us improve the overall website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
Google Privacy Policy
PayPal
Apache Cookie_check S_vi S_pers KHclI0EuY7AKSMgfvHI7J5E7hPtK DH4puLeRqX6BpunfdurQO8Swi28
These cookies are used in conjunction with the PayPal payment gateway used when paying for goods on this website.
PayPal Privacy Policy
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Dale & Co (Ancoats) Ltd (Dale Lifting & Handling)
Data Protection Terms and Conditions
These are the terms and conditions for the contract between:
-  us, Dale & Co (Ancoats) Ltd    (Registered Company Number 00610341)
-  you, our customer;
for us to supply goods or services as requested by you.
Data Protection
For the purposes of the contract, you are the 'datacontroller' and we are the 'data processor' for personal data processed in connection with the contract, as per the meanings given to them under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). In some circumstances we may also be a 'data controller' regarding the methods of processing data to facilitate the contract.
When we process personal data for the purpose of the contract we will do the following:
a) Do so only for the purpose of meeting our obligations under the contract, or where the law permits us to do so.
b) Comply with all relevant instructions or requests you give us about processing this personal data.
c) Take appropriate security measures to protect this personal data against unauthorised or unlawful processing, and accidental loss, destruction or damage.
d) Not allow this personal data to be transferred out of, or processed outside, the European Economic Area, unless we have taken such measures as are necessary to ensure the transfer is compliant with all            applicable data protection law.
e) Not pass this personal data to any third party (other than our sub-contractors and key service providers) unless there is a legal statutory obligation to do so or we have your permission in writing.
f)  Provide reasonable and timely assistance to assist you in dealing with data protectionrelated requests relating to data we hold, including to respond to any request from a data subject to exercise any of its rights under Applicable Data Protection Law and respond to any other correspondence, enquiry or complaint received from a data subject, regulator or other third party in connection with the data we hold.
g)  Inform you of any high-risk activities relating to your data.
h)  Inform you of any data breaches relating to your data without undue delay.
i)   Make sure that all our personnel who need access to this personal data for the purpose of the contract keep to this clause.
j)  Provide an encrypted credit card payment facility through Sage Pay or Paypal, or alternatively provide our bank details for direct payments into our account. If payment is to be taken over the phone this will be done by specially trained staff and credit card details will be imputed into an encrypted payment facility and not retained.
Statement dated 10 May 2018
Sign up to our newsletter for all the latest offers
Get Offers
Categories
By Brand
Lifting, Hoisting and Winching
Material Handling
Handrail Systems
© 2018 DLH Online | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Ecommerce Website Design by Evocus
Secure Payment
